All right, you guys, this
is one of the craziest houses
I've ever seen in my entire life.
We're gonna go up to them and
see what they were able to do
to be able to afford
this place out here in Atlanta.
Let's go see what they have to say.
Please wait while your call is connected.
Hey, how's it going?
Hey, question for you, sir.
I started a channel in Austin, Texas
that I grew to four million followers,
going all over the country,
just asking beautiful homeowners a few questions
on their best advice to the younger generation
of kids coming out of school.
Thought you had a beautiful house, man.
What if nobody could ask you
just a few quick questions for the channel?
Is that cool?
Yeah, sure.
Appreciate you, man.
Access granted.
What's going on, man?
How you doing?
What's up, boss?
Good, man.
How about yourself?
Good, good.
How long have you been in Atlanta for?
Been in Atlanta about,
well, over almost 14 years.
Yeah?
And I guess, what do you do for a living
to be able to afford this place?
Mysterio Entrepreneur.
How many businesses do you own?
Six businesses at the moment.
Six businesses.
Could we ask you a couple questions for the channel?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Give me one second there.
Appreciate you.
Across all these businesses,
what was the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
In a single year,
the most money I've ever made is 15 million.
15 million dollars.
How can somebody become a millionaire in 2024?
The city of Atlanta, Georgia
is home to nearly 20,000 millionaires.
And today, I'm going to be going all over
the wealthiest parts of Atlanta
to ask multi-millionaires
from eight to nine-figure entrepreneurs
how they became wealthy
and how you can start your path
to becoming financially free in 2024.
So with that being said,
let's get this video on the way.
All right, you guys,
my guy just pulled up in a Lamborghini.
We're going to go up and
see what he was able to do.
Come on, guys.
Excuse me, sir.
Quick question for you, man.
Is this your Lamborghini?
Yeah, yeah.
And what do you do for living out in Atlanta
to be able to afford a Lamborghini?
I own a marketing agency.
And how long have you been a business owner for?
Full-time entrepreneur,
last 15 years.
Marketing, last eight years.
And over these 15 years,
what's been the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
Last couple years,
a little bit over 10 million each year.
That's incredible.
Yeah.
And I guess, do you come from money?
Yeah, I wish.
Dabbing in jail since I was two for murder.
Kicked out of high school, college.
Fired from 10 jobs.
Born and raised in ghettos in West Philly.
Nah.
Yeah.
Not at all.
Now, I go all over the country
just asking business owners
their best advice to young entrepreneurs.
Is it cool if we ask
you a few questions for the channel?
Yeah, let's do it.
Awesome.
Are you a buyer or a seller?
I'm both.
Yeah.
I buy as much information as I can
to help me get better,
and I sell.
And I mean, I'm both.
Yeah.
But I like to be
a producer more than a consumer.
I think that's the other issue with people is
we're more of a consumers than we are producers.
We know more about LeBron's stats
than we know about our own stats.
We know more about what's going on in sports
than we know about what's going on.
Like, in this season,
I tell people, this is blinder season.
Like, I don't know.
I've been to the Kentucky Derby.
Every horse that races,
they got something called blinders.
One on the left, one on the right.
So they can't see what's going on
to the left or the right of them.
If everybody start focusing on your own race
and what's in front of you,
everything could change in a short period of time.
More than 90% of businesses
won't make it past five years.
What's the most common mistake
you see business owners make
that,
prevents them from scaling
and having that longevity?
I would say lack of marketing, right?
I tell people all the time,
you're extremely good at what you do,
but no one knows what you do.
If you are the best at this
and no one knows,
you're going to go out of business.
So you need to be spending
as much money as you can on marketing
and getting yourself out here
so everyone know you exist.
Would you say that if you lost a lot,
you can make it all back?
Well, 100%.
Because I got the mindset now
and I got the skill sets.
How old are you now?
36 years old.
36, yeah.
If you were to go back in time
and have a conversation
with your 20-year-old self,
if you were starting from zero,
what's the best advice
that you would give to your younger self?
The best advice I would say
is the biggest way to kill a big dream
is to introduce it to a small mind.
Guard who you share your goals and dreams with
because mind you,
you got your mom,
you got your dad,
you got family,
they love you.
So they only going to give you advice
to not hurt you.
That makes you feel good, right?
You need to go get advice
from people who are already crushing it,
people who are already a high level.
You want to become a millionaire,
you don't ask someone who's not it.
You want to start a business,
you don't ask your coworker.
How much sense does it make to say,
y'all want to go start a business,
you go into your job and say,
hey, I'm thinking about starting a business,
you think I should do it?
The answer will always be no.
Why?
Because they're at a place
where they don't want to commit to a business.
They don't want to commit to trying anything new.
So the biggest thing I could tell anybody
is if you want to become successful,
learn from someone who's already there
in the industry that they're in
that you want to learn about.
You got phenomenal advice, man.
Appreciate you, my friend.
So we caught my guy getting out of the Lamborghini,
heading into Dior
and he went from being broke
to creating an eight figure marketing agency
that did over $10 million this past year.
And what did he say?
The fastest way to kill a big dream
is to tell it to a small mind.
Great interview from a real legend.
He just dropped some phenomenal advice.
But with that being said,
let's go get this next interview.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
Have you ever been broke before?
Have I been what?
Sure.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And what do you do for living out in Atlanta?
Commercial real estate development.
How long have you been in the business for?
25 years.
Now people think you have
to have a lot of money
to get started out in real estate.
Would you agree with that?
Or like, what's that first move
someone can make without a
ton of money in real estate?
Yeah, unfortunately, real estate is expensive.
Yeah?
You do need some money.
What was the most amount of money
that you've ever made in a single year?
$100 million.
A couple hundred billion dollars.
How did you scale from eight to nine figures, right?
A lot of entrepreneurs,
they start a business,
they have a great idea,
they struggle to scale and grow.
What was your secret to scaling?
Look, if you go back
and look at all the businesses
that are really successful out there,
a lot of it has to do with timing.
Have you ever met a billionaire before?
Oh, hell yeah.
Yeah?
Unfortunately.
What do you notice consistently among billionaires?
Not even just billionaires.
They're not as smart as you think.
What do you mean by that?
Everybody thinks because you have a billion dollars,
that makes you smart.
What I mean by that is,
a lot of people get lucky.
It's not so much being a billionaire,
that matters.
It's like,
do you know the difference between values and beliefs?
What's that?
Beliefs are what you think is true.
Values are what you think are important.
Understanding your beliefs,
and then understanding your values.
Like, what do you believe in?
What do you think is important?
Focus on the things that are important.
What is the secret to
being able to raise capital, right?
In a competitive industry like real estate,
and entrepreneurship in general,
in terms of raising capital,
any advice to people out there?
Maybe it's for development,
for a project.
What I think will shock most people,
not wealthy people,
or some of the people you just named,
is right now,
there is more money out there in the world,
looking for a good business plan,
than the,
inverse.
There are not as many good business plans,
as what you think.
And the people who have capital,
they can look at a business plan quickly,
and tell.
Just like,
you know,
watching Shark Tank,
right?
They know what does and doesn't make sense.
They understand margins,
they understand cost structures,
they understand when somebody doesn't know the details.
So,
raising capital is,
you got to start with like,
a really good business plan,
that has a legitimate pathway to growth.
You have to be able to,
show why this is going to be worth the effort.
Why is this money,
going to come back with a return,
that makes sense for the person investing in it.
How,
old are you now?
I'm about to turn 56.
Yeah.
How old were you,
when you became a millionaire?
55 and a half.
No,
I'm kidding.
I have no idea,
because I don't really track that stuff.
It just isn't that important to me.
Right.
But I'll tell you this much,
I've been happy for 40 years,
and that's a hell of
a lot more important to me.
Yeah.
I love that.
What is the secret to finding that happiness,
right?
That inner peace inside,
Because like you said.
That's a really good question.
I mean,
that in itself is,
you know,
there's another saying that says,
like,
if you do something you love,
you'll never work a day in your life.
Well,
when I went through that transition,
I realized I'd fell into that restaurant job,
and I was very successful at it,
and I was like,
what did I learn from it?
I learned how to manage resources,
people,
time,
money,
expectation,
and I was really good at it.
And I was like,
okay,
so I understand how to manage resources.
So what is it that I want to do,
where I can take that skill set,
and go do that?
And what I decided was,
real estate development.
And I enjoyed every minute of it,
and I look back on it,
and I just feel good about it,
because it was something I really enjoyed,
and I was doing it with really smart,
capable people.
But like,
you've got to,
you've got to figure out like,
what makes you happy.
And some people,
it's golfing every day.
Some people,
it's like sitting out on their porch,
on a piece of property,
where they don't have to see,
hear,
or know that anybody else exists,
for 10 miles away.
I mean,
it's different for everybody.
Focus on that,
and the rest is good.
Yeah,
thank you so much for your time.
James Dumlip,
sir.
So we walked up on a nine-figure,
commercial real estate developer,
out here in Atlanta,
and that interview just goes to show,
there is endless amounts of capital,
and money circulating in the entire world.
You just have to come up with the right ideas,
that people are willing to back,
and get behind,
and you can create something amazing.
Phenomenal interview, man.
Let's go get this next one.
All right, you guys.
This is one of the craziest houses,
I've ever seen in my entire life.
We're going to go up to them,
and see what they were able to do,
to be able to afford this place,
out here in Atlanta.
Let's go see what they have to say.
Please wait while your call is connected.
Hey, how's it going?
Hey, question for you, sir.
I started a channel in Austin, Texas,
that I grew to four million followers,
going all over the country,
just asking,
beautiful homeowners,
a few questions on their best advice,
to the younger generation,
to kids coming out of school.
Thought you had a beautiful house, man.
Wanted to know if we could ask you,
just a few quick questions for the channel.
Is that cool?
Yeah, sure.
Appreciate you, man.
Access granted.
What's going on, man?
How you doing?
What's up, boss?
Good, man.
How about yourself?
I'm good.
How long have you been in Atlanta for?
I've been in Atlanta about,
a little over almost 14 years.
Yeah?
And I guess,
what do you do for a living,
to be able to afford this place?
I'm a serial entrepreneur.
How many businesses do you own?
Six businesses at the moment.
Six businesses.
Could we ask you a couple questions,
for the channel?
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Give me one second here.
Appreciate you.
Across all these businesses,
what was the most amount of money,
that you've ever made in a single year?
In a single year,
the most money I've ever made,
is 15 million.
15 million dollars.
Are you a buyer or a seller?
I'm a seller.
Why is that?
Listen,
somebody has to consume,
somebody has to produce.
I always rather be on the end of producing.
One thing about it,
I always,
my mentors told me early on,
more people got rich,
during the gold rush,
selling shovels,
than looking for gold.
How old are you?
How old were you,
when you became a millionaire?
I made my first million at 29.
Yes.
And have you ever been broke before?
A thousand percent.
I was homeless and broke.
And I worked from 24,
up until I was about 26,
just getting back on my feet,
trying to find different ways,
and building everything out.
For somebody broke right now,
for somebody at rock bottom,
what is an actionable step,
that they can take,
to get really serious,
about becoming financially free,
like yourself?
It'll never come from money.
Whenever somebody comes to me,
and say,
hey,
you know,
I'm flat broke.
You don't have a financial issue.
It's a personal issue.
You have traumas,
or things like that.
That you're dealing with,
and healing,
that you need to deal with,
to overcome.
Because for you to get into a situation,
where you have no money,
you're making bad decisions.
You're making bad choices,
on a daily basis.
You have bad habits,
that you need to correct.
What are the things,
that I have to cut out?
And once I can identify those things,
I can build on it,
and become a better person,
as an individual.
And then you look at learning,
and then you look at learning skill sets,
that can contribute to you.
You know,
if you flat broke on rock bottom,
I will pick up,
and learn how to sell.
Right?
Once I get to a complacent point,
where I'm okay,
because I don't want to be a toxic person,
and have negative traits on me.
And then go try to sell,
and develop on top of it.
You can't put sugar on shit.
So you have to get rid of it,
and go,
hey,
now I'm okay.
I can start to build properly,
on top of this foundation.
What do you think is more important,
mindset or skill set?
The mindset.
Because the mindset,
will allow you to pick the proper skill set.
Because with a bad mindset,
you'll say,
oh man,
people are great at sales,
I'm a sale.
Yeah,
but you're an introvert.
You have the wrong mindset,
because you're just thinking that,
okay,
I'm just going to go do,
whatever somebody else is doing.
I'm going to go do e-commerce.
Oh,
you know what?
I'm going to go be an online influencer,
but you're not attractive.
You don't like speaking.
You don't like,
you know,
you don't have a bright personality.
You won't be consistent in posts.
Your mindset will allow you to identify,
who you are,
what's your strong points,
what's your weaknesses.
I know my weaknesses,
and I know my strong points.
I strengthen my weaknesses on purpose,
but I flourish in my strong points,
intentionally.
And that's one thing that we have to do.
So that's where mindset comes in.
It's like,
your mindset will allow you,
to not make bad decisions,
thinking that,
oh yeah,
if I just go learn how to work,
I could be a millionaire.
And it's like,
yo bro,
you got one arm.
It's like a bad mindset.
You just think about money,
but it's like,
yo,
you're not physically equipped,
or capable,
to do this.
And as an eight figure entrepreneur,
what's been the best financial advice,
that you've ever received,
throughout your career?
Spend that shit.
Spend it in ways,
that bring back impact money,
as a tool.
Spend it to,
further your information,
to further your network,
to get in certain different environments,
that you're not privy to.
What's the deepest life quote,
that you've ever heard?
More money,
more problems.
Why is that?
Because the things,
that come with financial success,
is things that you could never imagine.
You see it on movies,
you see it on TV.
But the things,
that come with this,
the traumas,
the experiences,
the day-to-day life,
everything is great.
But it's a lot of things,
that you cannot predict.
That you think,
becoming financially free,
is great.
But the different things,
where you have to mentally grow,
and where you mentally grow through.
Once you get there,
you realize that,
okay,
it took work,
to get here.
And you look at everybody,
and you can't help,
but to judge.
That if,
you only did this,
and you know it.
If you did this,
this,
and third,
you wouldn't have those problems.
You now have to face that,
and deal with family problems,
friends,
and you've changed.
You do change.
You get to see more,
you've experienced,
a different level of life.
And the hardest part,
is that everything around you changes.
Everybody around you changes.
And that's something for me,
that I've struggled with dealing with.
It's like,
okay,
accepting people for who they are,
where they are,
but realizing,
they can't accept me,
for where I'm at.
You got amazing advice, man.
Thank you so much for your time.
This video was insane,
to make you guys,
some of the craziest interviews,
that we've ever done.
But I want you to like,
and subscribe,
for amazing content,
we have coming,
very,
very soon.
And click the link,
in the description below,
to join the Hard Knocks newsletter,
right now.
Because we're sending out,
weekly updates,
insights,
and lessons,
from the world's top entrepreneurs,
directly to you.
So click the link below,
to join the Hard Knocks newsletter,
because you do not want to miss out on this.
But guys,
that's a wrap on today's video.
Be sure to click right here,
to watch our full video,
going all over New York City,
asking multi-millionaires,
how you can start your path,
to becoming financially free,
in 2024.
We'll see you guys,
in the next video.